(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(air whooshing)
(child laughing)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music continues)
(gentle music)
(gentle music continues)
(dramatic music)
(gunshot blasting)
(pensive music)
(arm rasping)
(Sean gasping)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music continues)
(Sean sighing)
(gentle music)
(computers beeping)
(vocalists singing in Latin)
- You getting anything?
- No.
(gun clanking)
Hey, folks, what is this, a picnic?
Come on, let's go, man.
We got 10 minutes to go.
(vocalists singing in Latin)
- Punch me out, man.
- You got it.
(computer beeping)
(dramatic music)
(computer continues beeping)
(vocalists singing in Latin)
(device beeping)
Any word from the LAPD intelligence
if there is such a thing?
Not yet, sir.
- Of course not, 'cause we're
a covert anti-terrorism team
that is so secret that
when we snap our fingers,
nothing happens.
(device beeping)
(dramatic music continues)
Sheriff's department, airport police?
- Still waiting, but Interpol
insists he's in Tripoli.
Yeah, well, you, you trust,
you trust that billion-dollar
satellite, okay?
I'll trust a $10 snitch at this point.
[Tito] Sean, look.
What?
- [Tito] Why don't you just
give 'em a little break, okay?
- We'll take a break when
the case breaks, okay?
(upbeat discordant music)
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah,
hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ For the Lord God Omnipotent reigneth ♪
(hands smacking)
(notebook thudding)
♪ And he shall reign for ever and ever ♪
I don't really enjoy the "Messiah."
In fact, I think it's fucking boring.
But your voice makes even a hack
like Handel (whimpering)
seem like a genius.
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah,
hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
(Castor screaming)
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
- Victor, when we, when
we put this thing to bed,
you, you can brand the
Fourth Amendment on my butt.
Thank you.
- Sir, excuse me, your
wife is on line one.
Sean.
A jet was just chartered,
Anderson Airfield.
Guess who paid the bill
in cash, Pollux Troy.
Put one of our people on that plane.
- [Tito] Wait, we still
got no sign of Castor.
Pollux doesn't fly without big brother.
Now, come on.
(pensive music)
(jet engine humming)
(pensive music continues)
(jacket rustling)
26 minutes late.
Casing didn't fit right.
See, I told you Goddamn Dietrich would try
to pawn off some cheap
shit North Korean plastic.
Casing fit like a condom.
You didn't deviate from the plan, did you,
(gum rattling)
Pollux?
- Well, how long do
you want me to sit here
twiddling my thumbs?
Paid for the jet, saved us some time.
- That's what the boys are
for, to hide our famous faces.
(jet engine humming)
Buddy, I didn't love you so
much, I'd have to kill you, bro.
I hate it when you call me, bro.
(pensive music continues)
- You guys are paid to
protect him from everybody,
including himself.
And stay away from downtown on the 18th.
It's gonna be a little, uh, smoggy.
Okay, my passengers are here.
I gotta go.
(pensive music continues)
Let's go, let's go.
I'm bored. Let's go.
- Here you go.
- Hmm, bravo.
- Would you like anything
else once we're airborne?
Oh, peach.
Sit. Come on.
Mm.
You know, I can, uh,
eat a peach for hours.
(Castor exhales)
Um, if I were to send you flowers,
where would I, uh, (laughs)
wait, let me rephrase.
If I were to let you suck my tongue,
would you be grateful?
Oh.
(engine humming)
(dramatic music)
(tires screeching)
There's someone on the runway.
(siren wailing)
Get off of me.
(sirens wailing)
(dramatic music continues)
(helicopter whirring)
Archer.
(gun clanking)
FBI.
(Pollux grunting)
(briefcase thudding)
(fist thudding)
(gun clanking)
This is a very big gun.
Fly the fucking plane.
(sirens wailing)
(dramatic music continues)
Come on.
That's it.
(helicopter whirring)
Come on. Let's go.
- Goddammit, don't play
chicken with a Goddamn jet.
(engine revving)
Come on.
(gun clanking)
He's got Winters, Goddammit.
[Tito] Damn it, Sean.
(engine roaring)
(tires screeching)
All units, pin 'em in.
(helicopter whirring)
Close in on 'em.
(door clattering)
One of yours, Sean?
(gunshot blasting)
Shit.
(body thudding)
(tires screeching)
(doors slamming)
(helicopter whirring)
(dramatic music continues)
Out, come on. Go, go.
Goddammit, Sean.
(helicopter whirring)
(dramatic music continues)
(gun clanking)
Take off now.
(metal clanging)
Fly.
- I can't.
Fly, bitch.
(engine revving)
(metal clanging)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
All units, locked and ready.
Follow Archer's lead.
(helicopter whirring)
(dramatic music continues)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(explosion blasting)
(alarm blaring)
What the fuck are you doing?
There's an engine out.
We gotta stop.
(gunshot blasting)
(pilot grunting)
(dramatic music continues)
(helicopter whirring)
(engine whistling)
(glass shattering)
(explosion blasting)
(helicopter whirring)
(sirens wailing)
- Move, move, move.
- Get back.
Back up.
- Cover me.
(feet thudding)
(guns clanking)
(explosion blasting)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(officer screaming)
- [Officer] Go, go.
(gunshots blasting)
(officer screaming)
Pollux.
(gunshots blasting)
(gas hissing)
[Pollux] Cas.
Get over here.
(body thudding)
(Pollux grunting)
(foot thudding)
Back him to me. Back him to me.
(body thudding)
He's mine.
(glass shattering)
(gunshot blasting)
(body thudding)
(handcuffs clanging)
Cas.
(electricity hissing)
Secure the hangar.
(brooding music)
(footsteps plodding)
(gun clanking)
Berkley, down.
(gunshots blasting)
(gun clanking)
Down.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music)
(footsteps plodding)
(guns clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(metal clanging)
(electricity hissing)
(engine roaring)
Give up, Castor. Your time's up.
(Castor laughing)
Well, you better hit me, Sean,
'cause you only got one bullet left.
So do you.
Wow, we've got something in common.
We both know our guns.
What we don't have in common is
that I don't care if I live, and you do.
Sean, that hurts.
You're not having any fun, are ya, Sean?
Why don't you come with
us, try terrorism for hire?
We'll blow some shit up.
It's more fun.
- Shut the fuck up.
You watch your fucking mouth.
I'm about to unleash the
biblical plague Hell-A deserves,
but I'll give this shithole a break
if my brother and I walk.
- Bullshit.
- Oh, oh, no.
L, I see, I see.
You, you, you think I'm bluffing.
Maybe I am, but then maybe I'm not.
More importantly, what would
you do with me locked up?
You'd drive your wife and kid crazy.
Say, how is your daughter, anyway?
Is she ripening by now?
Your darling Janie, your
little peach, is she ripe?
(Castor imitating dog whimpering)
(Castor screaming)
(gun clanking)
Okay, okay,
policeman, don't shoot me. (laughing)
I'm scared, Seanie. (laughing)
Well, I think you better pull the trigger
because I don't give a fuck.
(knife rasping)
♪ I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready for the big ride, baby ♪
(foot thudding)
(knife clanking)
(dramatic music)
(Castor grunting)
(elbow thudding)
(engine roaring)
(body thudding)
(air whooshing)
(hand thudding)
(engine whistling)
(footsteps plodding)
- Well, Sean, looks like
Elvis done left the building.
(Sean sighing)
(engine humming)
[Jamie] It wasn't my fault.
Why won't you ever be on my side?
I am always on your side,
but you have to give me a chance.
Now what?
(Eve sighing)
She was suspended again.
Some kid made a crack about her clothes.
She started a fight.
[Jamie] That's right, Dad.
Don't even ask me what happened.
- Okay, what happened?
(pensive music)
Oh, I see.
(footsteps plodding)
Not like you would believe me anyway.
- Jamie, look, it, it,
it's not easy, okay?
I mean, look. (sighs)
You change the way you look every week
and, and, and the way you act.
Who are you supposed to be now?
I'm supposed to be me.
Not like you have a clue who I am anyway.
(footsteps plodding)
(door clattering)
(Sean sighing)
Uh, I have to work tonight.
I called to tell you, but I
was on hold for 10 minutes,
and I couldn't wait any longer.
I got him, Eve.
(pensive music)
It's over?
It's over.
Oh, Sean.
(gentle music)
I'll make it up to you and Jamie.
I promise.
I'll put in for a desk job.
We'll all, all do counseling,
sit down, talk about Mikey.
I'll do it, anything you want.
(Eve exhales)
[Eve] I just want you. (laughs)
(laughing) Well, good,
'cause that's what you're gonna get.
(Eve laughing)
Happy?
Uh, yes, yeah.
(gentle music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
[Coworker] Hold up.
(coworkers clapping)
What is all this?
Sir, the CIA sent this over.
I didn't know they catered.
Send it back.
No, wait.
(somber music)
How 'bout, uh, what about
to Anderson, Montgomery,
Berkley, Pincus,
Gianelli, Winters?
(bottle thudding)
(somber music continues)
(computer beeping)
(dramatic music)
(fingers tapping)
(computer beeping)
(door clattering)
How's Loomis?
Uh, he's gonna need a little surgery,
but, uh, he'll be okay.
What's up?
Special ops, (laughs) they want a word.
Aw, forget it.
I don't have the time.
Better make time, Sean.
Recovered from the jet wreckage.
Found in Pollux Troy's briefcase.
(suspenseful music)
(disk clattering)
(sultry music)
(woman moaning)
Porcelain casing, thermal cloak,
nerve gas, and biological payload.
It's enough to flatten a square mile.
Then, depending on the prevailing winds,
the fallout'll be a tad
worse than Gulf War syndrome.
A biblical, a biblical plague to LA.
Fuck. (screams)
(hand thudding)
Where is he?
Where is Pollux Troy?
(pensive music)
(paper thudding)
Why draw the schematic
if you're not gonna build the bomb, hmm?
- [Pollux] What, is it now
a crime in this country
to exercise the mind?
- I'm interested in bomb-
- I won't say another word
until I see my brother.
Any progress?
- I need about 10 minutes
alone with this guy.
Ah, give it a rest.
You got Castor.
Just go home.
(Sean sighing)
Look, we're not gonna evacuate
the city on your hunch.
- Look, I know Castor too
well for this to be a hunch.
You know what?
Just, just run the goddamn
Bureau any way ya like.
(dramatic music)
(door slamming)
(Sean sighing)
I could put an agent in his cell.
Maybe Pollux will let it slip.
Oh, come on.
He's a paranoid sociopath.
The only person he'd talk to
about that bomb is his brother,
and he's dead.
There is one other possibility.
(suspenseful music)
(door buzzing and clattering)
Oh, God, you're keeping him alive.
Relax, Archer.
He's a turnip.
(cigarette hissing)
Oh.
- What if you could
walk into Erewhon Prison
and give Pollux a nice, big,
brotherly hug as Castor Troy?
- I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Let me try.
Malcolm Walsh.
I run the bio-cover unit for special ops.
I know who you are.
But you don't know what I can do.
- Uh-
- Physical alteration.
Augmentation.
- [Hollis] Dr. Walsh
can alter the likeness,
even the voice of a government witness.
I think you'll recognize this patient.
(suspenseful music continues)
We had to build your friend Loomis
a whole new ear from scratch.
(fingers tapping)
(lasers buzzing)
What we're suggesting for you, Archer,
isn't a permanent transplant like that,
just a temporary trade.
Come here.
(fingers tapping)
With the new anti-inflammatories,
healing takes days, not weeks.
Your blood types won't match,
but Pollux won't know that.
Height difference is negligible.
Skin pigment, eye pigment,
both almost identical.
We'll use laser shears for the hairline,
microplugs for body hair.
We'll do an abdominoplasty,
take care of those, uh, love handles.
But all that's the easy part.
(laser buzzing)
Here's the real science.
This is a state-of-the-art
morphogenetic template.
The inside is modeled on your skull,
the outside exactly like Troy's.
Then, we fit his face on top,
not a replica, but the real thing.
Then, we simply connect the muscles,
tear ducts, and nerve endings.
So, you wanna take his face and mine-
Borrow.
The procedure's completely reversible.
- You, you think that I
want to do this? (laughs)
No, no.
- There's no one else, Sean.
No.
- You have lived and breathed
Castor Troy for years.
I'll get his gang to talk.
That's what I do.
- What if you can't?
The bomb will blow, and
Castor Troy will win.
(body thudding)
(items clattering)
Get out.
Go ahead.
Wipe your ass.
Damn, what the hell is that smell?
He shit in his pants.
Where's Dietrich?
(chair rasping)
Hello, Sasha. (sighs)
When was the last time
you saw Castor Troy?
Who cares? He's dead.
Answer the question.
I know my rights.
I don't have to answer shit.
You're right, but know this.
You're a convicted felon on probation
for harboring Castor Troy.
(suspenseful music)
One phone call from me,
and your son will end up in a foster home.
(Sasha sighs)
- I understand why you
would use such a threat.
But you try to take him away
from me, I swear to you.
I haven't seen him for years.
(hand thudding)
(switch clicking)
(lighter clicking)
(door clattering)
This reeks of you.
It's got your signature all over it.
- Maybe, but you ain't got
nothing on me, and you know it.
- Maybe so, but I can keep
you within city limits,
or I can talk to your sister again.
She's right outside.
Only this time, I'll be nice.
Hey, Sean.
How's your dead son?
(Dietrich laughing)
(body thudding)
(gun clanking)
(dramatic music)
I don't know anything.
Okay, okay, I heard
something about the 18th,
but that's all I know.
(gun clanking)
(door clattering)
(Sean sighing)
Great, so we got a date.
Now, where the hell's the damn bomb?
Only Pollux Troy'll know that.
It's your call, Sean.
Does Lazarro know your plan?
No, this is a black-bag operation,
strictly off the books.
You can't tell Lazarro, and
you can't tell your wife.
(suspenseful music)
Oh, God.
What are you asking me to do?
Okay, let's see.
You're asking me to, to
break the law, risk my neck.
And you're asking me to put
in the dark all the people
that love me and trust me.
(suspenseful music continues)
(Sean sighing)
I'll do it.
(door clattering)
(engine humming)
(dog barking)
(latch clicking)
(bedding rustling)
Mm, Sean.
Sorry I woke you.
- No, I'm glad it's you
that woke me (laughs)
and not a phone call telling
me you won't be coming home.
But that's a fear I can
finally let go of, huh?
(lips smacking)
(Eve exhaling)
Oh, it's all right, Sean.
It's okay.
I keep,
I keep wanting to move
this over here, you know?
If it had only been an,
an inch to the left,
Mikey'd be alive.
And you wouldn't be.
Sean, things are gonna get
better now that you're home.
The scar won't move, but
it will heal if you let it.
Everything will be better now
that he's forever out of our lives.
(Sean sighing)
(gentle music)
Eve, if I told you that I realized
that, that this thing won't fully end
until I did one last thing,
Eve, something vital.
- Okay, uh, you're going
back on assignment again?
This one last time.
Come on, Eve.
- "I'm not going anywhere,"
that's what you told me.
Oh.
- You don't need me to
tell you what to do, Sean.
You never have, so go, but go now.
(gentle music continues)
(lips smacking)
(Tito sighing)
(switch clicking)
Sean, I changed my mind.
This is a suicide mission.
Yeah, I know, I know.
You know, maybe this, uh, this doctor,
if he, if he, if he can do even half
of what he says he can
do, uh, maybe it'll work.
I don't know.
I'd become Castor Troy, be in control.
That's the part that scares me.
(Sean laughing)
- Yeah.
(door buzzing and clattering)
Doctor, I have, uh, something.
I have this scar
that, uh, that, that if
you can put this back
after, after all this is over,
it, it's important to me.
It's, it's like a reminder.
Sure.
(pensive music)
Tito, please hold this for me, please.
Okay, let's go.
(door buzzing and clattering)
(switch clicking)
(suspenseful music)
(wheels clattering)
(machine beeping)
(machine whirring)
(fingers tapping)
(machine beeping)
(laser buzzing)
(fingers tapping)
(computer beeping)
(machine whirring)
(dramatic music)
(computer beeping)
(machine whirring)
(machine beeping)
(liquid sloshing)
(dramatic music continues)
(scissors rasping)
(computer beeping)
(laser buzzing)
(machine whirring)
(machine beeping)
(machine whirring and beeping)
(dramatic music continues)
(machine beeping and whirring)
(air whooshing)
(machine continues beeping)
(bandages rustling)
(pensive music)
(metal clanging)
Hey, you okay?
Come on. Talk to me, Sean.
(Sean whimpering)
(coat hanger thudding)
(glass shattering)
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
Sean.
- Fuck you.
- Sean.
Sean, come on. Sit down.
Sit down. Sit down.
Sean, Sean, Archer.
You're Sean Archer.
Sean Archer.
(air whooshing)
(hand thudding)
- When this is over, I
want you to take this face
and burn it.
Hey, I still sound like me.
- I've implanted a
microchip on your larynx.
It's fantastic, but
you'll have to be careful.
Pressure, sharp blow,
even a violent sneeze could dislodge it.
Just repeat what you hear.
- [Castor] Peach, I can
eat a peach for hours.
Peach, I can eat a peach for hours.
(computer beeping)
There's a scratchy tickle.
- [Castor] Peach, I can
eat a peach for hours.
(computer beeping)
Peach, I can eat a peach for hours.
[Dr. Walsh] Once again.
(computer beeping)
Perfect.
Now, Sean, six days until the 18th.
The clock's ticking, and so is the bomb.
(dramatic music)
(timer whizzing)
(helicopter whirring)
You got two days to get Pollux to talk.
Either way, Miller
comes in, pulls you out.
You got me?
- All right, move it.
- Let's do it.
[Tito] What's the matter?
Face itches.
(suspenseful music)
(helicopter whirring)
You all right?
Come on. Let's go.
- Archer's gonna be
pissed when he comes back
from his training op and finds out.
The guy is knee-deep in a Georgia swamp?
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
(door clattering)
(pensive music)
(footsteps plodding)
- You are now the property
of Erewhon Prison,
a citizen of nowhere.
The Geneva Convention is void here.
Amnesty International
doesn't know we exist.
When I say your ass belongs to me,
I mean exactly that.
(metal clanging)
This entire prison's
one big magnetic field.
The boots tell us where you are.
621 to population.
(footsteps plodding)
(dramatic music)
(inmates chattering indistinctly)
(footsteps plodding)
(pensive music)
Hey, what's the matter, pal?
(laughing) Don't you
remember the little people?
- Burke Hicks.
- Oh, yeah.
I bust,
believe Sean Archer busted you
for stalking the UN Secretary General.
Oh, no, Archer framed me.
I ain't had nothing to
do with that. (laughs)
Word was you got wasted.
(suspenseful music)
- You wanna see what wasted
looks like, little man?
[Inmates] Ooh.
Pollux.
(fists thudding)
(dramatic music)
(inmates cheering)
(body thudding)
(computer beeping)
(fist thudding)
(Sean groaning)
(inmates cheering)
(footsteps plodding)
(foot thudding)
(Sean grunting)
(fist thudding)
[Guard] Out of the way.
- [Guard] Central, there's a
disturbance in the population.
Go to lockdown.
- Hold that lockdown.
(fist thudding)
(inmates cheering)
(body thudding)
(elbow thudding)
(fist thudding)
(dramatic music continues)
(inmates cheering)
Come on, you pussy.
(foot thudding)
(metal clanging)
You watch your fucking mouth.
(inmates cheering)
Watch your fucking mouth.
(fists thudding)
(foot thudding)
(elbow thudding)
(metal clanging)
'Cause I'm Castor Troy, yeah.
I'm Castor Troy.
(inmates cheering)
Whoo.
I'm Castor Troy.
(fist thudding)
Yeah, whoo.
(foot thudding)
(inmates cheering)
Yeah.
(foot thudding)
(Sean grunting)
Whoo.
(Sean screaming)
(hands thudding)
(body thudding)
(gentle music)
(inmates cheering)
Lock 'em down.
(computer beeping)
(electricity buzzing)
(bodies thudding)
I stop the fights, not you.
That's two strikes for you, Dubov.
One more, you know where you're going.
When I get out of here-
If you get outta here.
I'm gonna have you fired.
(inmates laughing)
(footsteps plodding)
(machine beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(dramatic music)
(machine beeping)
(suspenseful music)
(bandages rustling)
(blood squelching)
(feet thudding)
(Castor coughing)
(Castor moaning)
(Castor screaming)
(blinds clanking)
[Castor] Lars, it's me.
Believe it.
Someone (coughs) they took, switched my,
fuck, some fucking (coughing)
but it's cool.
We're gonna deal with it. (laughing)
Oh, yes, we're gonna deal with it.
(engine humming)
(suspenseful music continues)
(tires screeching)
(keys jangling)
(dramatic opera music)
(footsteps plodding)
(door clattering)
- What's this about?
- Dr. Walsh.
I was just, uh, enjoying some
of your greatest hits here.
(door clattering)
Oh, oh, I hope you don't mind.
L, I, uh, I partook of your groovy, uh,
(pills rattling)
your groovy painkillers.
You know, this is fabulous work.
This is, this is, oh, (laughs) bravo.
(Castor laughing)
(hands clapping)
Bra-fucking-vo.
Oh, God, this is excellent, bravo.
Bravo.
What do you want?
(hands clapping)
Take one goddam guess.
(footsteps plodding)
(birds chirping)
I wish they'd play some
of those salmon spawning scenes again.
I found them intensely erotic.
Ah, fucking nature channel.
One more waterfall, I'm
gonna foam at the mouth.
It's like they're begging us to riot.
Excuse me.
(birds chirping)
Not feeling very
coordinated lately, are you?
Look, bro, you gotta help me.
I am so fried.
If the psychos in here
find out I'm misfiring,
we're both gonna be dead meat.
Shock treatment?
What's the matter with you?
Did they operate?
I was in a coma.
Jesus, you're still so fucking paranoid.
Aren't they giving you
your medication in here?
What was my medication?
(brooding music)
- Pollux, I hand-fed you
those pills for years.
Vivex, I haven't forgotten that.
It's just everything else.
It's senses, my reflexes, my memory.
It's, uh, it's like a tab of bad Quantrex.
I don't even know why that
fucking yeti jumped me yesterday.
Dubov?
You had a sex sandwich with
his wife and his sister
the night he was sent here.
I guess that explains why he's so upset.
Wow.
(both laughing)
We're gonna blow up LA, bro.
Ain't it cool?
- Oh, right, rub my nose
in it, why don't you?
$10-million design, and now
those militia nutjobs get
to keep their cash.
It's so fucking unfair.
That bomb you built does
deserve an audience.
It's a work of art.
It belongs in the Louvre.
Yes, it does.
Oh, well.
I guess the LA Convention
Center'll have to do.
(pensive music)
What?
- Thank you.
- For what?
(dramatic music)
You are so fucking pathetic.
(panel beeping)
(door clattering and squeaking)
[Guard] You got a visitor.
(door squeaking)
(feet plodding)
(electricity buzzing)
(alarm blaring)
(door rasping)
(brooding music)
(brooding music continues)
(newspaper rustling)
Ooh, wee, you're good-looking.
You're hot.
It's like looking in a mirror, only not.
(footsteps plodding)
Troy?
Now, that is between us, okay?
But you were, uh-
In a coma?
Nothing like having your face
cut off to disturb your sleep.
Read the newspaper lately?
(dramatic music)
(gasoline sloshing)
(officers whimpering)
You killed them?
- (laughs) Well, beats
paying the bill, huh?
Come on, I mean, uh, if a
face-lift costs five grand,
see anything ya like?
(gasoline sloshing)
Tito.
(lighter clanking)
(fire roaring)
- I torched all the evidence
that proves you're you, okay?
(laughing) So, wow, looks
like you're gonna be in here
for the next hundred years.
(Sean whimpering)
Now, I have got to go.
I've got a government job to abuse
and a lonely wife to fuck.
Oh, did I say that?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't, make love to.
Oh, God, I miss that face.
(Castor grunting)
- Die, die.
(door clattering)
(electricity buzzing)
(Sean grunting)
(baton thudding)
(dramatic music continues)
(feet thudding)
(Sean grunting)
[Watson] Sorry, Agent Archer.
- No, don't you worry
about it, Mr. Walton.
Clearly, he's, uh, had
a traumatic childhood,
and, uh, thank you.
♪ What's giving you the will to
live is looking for revenge ♪
Look at this place.
I'm in hell.
I may never get a hard-on again.
(latch clicking)
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
(tires screeching)
Oh, yes, there we go.
(engine revving)
(tires screeching)
(window buzzing)
(pensive music)
(door clattering)
- Well, I suppose it was
only a matter of time
before you forgot where we lived.
Come on. Give me a break.
Every house on this block looks the same.
Then, I spotted you, Eve,
my one and only Eve.
So how was your vital assignment?
Which one was that?
(Eve laughs)
How should I know, Sean?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yes, the, um,
the out-of-body experience, yes, that one.
Where you going, hmm?
To the hospital.
No, no, what's the matter?
Sean, come on.
- Oh, what?
- Quit teasing me.
Stop it.
I'm still really hurt, okay?
There are leftovers in the fridge.
- No, no, I want to stay
hungry for you, my peach.
Give me that tongue.
- (laughing) Sean, come on.
What are you doing?
- What does Evie want?
- Eve, I hate to see ya go,
but I love to watch you leave.
(door clattering)
(Castor laughing)
(keys jangling)
(pictures rustling)
(Castor sighing)
(drawer clattering)
(pages rustling)
"Date night fizzled again.
We haven't made love in two months."
What a loser.
(diary thudding)
(Castor sighing)
(upbeat music)
♪ Come here, Sister ♪
♪ Papa's in the swing ♪
Got your e-mail, Karl.
The poem you sent me was pretty kinky.
♪ About that new breed, babe ♪
Hmm, the plot thickens.
♪ He ain't no drag ♪
♪ Papa's got a brand new bag ♪
- Hang on a second.
(hand thudding)
♪ Come here, mama ♪
I'll have to call you back.
(phone beeping)
♪ And dig this crazy scene ♪
You're not respecting my boundaries.
- I'm coming in, Janie.
- Janie?
♪ But this line is pretty clean ♪
I don't think you heard me, Jamie.
You got something that I crave.
♪ Papa's got a brand new bag ♪
♪ He's doing the jerk ♪
♪ He's doing the fly ♪
♪ Don't play him cheap ♪
- Clarissa left those here.
Well, I won't tell mom if you don't.
(lighter clicking)
♪ The mashed potato ♪
When did you start smoking?
- You'll be seeing a lot
of changes around here.
♪ Papa's in the swing ♪
Papa's got a brand new bag, ow.
♪ He ain't too hip now ♪
(Jamie laughs)
♪ But I can dig that new breed ♪
♪ Ooh, I'll do the swing ♪
♪ You do the twist just like this ♪
(footsteps plodding)
- Bye, Brother, drop me
a line sometime. (laughs)
- [Watson] Gonna be kind of
lonely with Pollux gone, huh?
Pollux what?
- That big-shit cop,
Archer, cut him a deal
for turning state's evidence.
Your brother's been released.
(dramatic music)
(hands thudding)
I'm Sean Archer.
There is a bomb at the
LA Convention Center.
I'm Sean Archer and,
ow.
(foot thudding)
(body thudding)
(dramatic music continues)
♪ Tiramisu, tiramisu ♪
(door clattering)
Sir, we just wanted you to know-
We're all really sorry about Tito.
Oh, hey, shit happens, you know?
So is our star witness talking?
- (scoffs) Yeah, about what
kind of mustard he likes
on his tongue sandwiches.
- If that bomb is out there,
we're almost outta time.
Hmm.
(door clattering)
Archer.
You made a deal with Pollux Troy.
That isn't like you.
- Well, when all else
fails, fresh tactics.
Fresh?
Well, let me tell you my fresh tactic.
From now on everything to do
with this case goes
through me, understood?
Good, thanks.
(switch clicking)
(door clattering)
- You're supposed to be snitching
and making me look good.
- Look good?
- Mm-hmm.
Seeing that face on you makes me afraid
my tiramisu might come back up.
Well, think about me, this nose,
this hair, this ridiculous chin.
(Castor sighing)
Brother, we're going straight.
- Oh, my goodness, did you
exchange brains as well?
- The first thing I need
you to confess to is
the location of the bomb.
What about our $10 million?
- What about when I
become an American hero
for defusing the bomb?
What's that worth?
You know that, thank you,
next question. (laughing)
You're not the only one in
this family with brains.
- No, although now I am the
only one with the looks.
Touche.
(sirens wailing)
(dramatic music)
- [Officer] This is an
emergency evacuation.
Let's go, police, let's go, let's go.
(brooding music)
(device beeping)
(timer whizzing)
- Any ideas?
- Yeah, run.
Sir, it's protected by a tamper switch,
and it'll take us hours to bypass.
Evacuate your team, Captain.
No, but, sir, we can't, we can't disarm.
Leave.
(footsteps plodding)
(timer whizzing)
(mellow music)
(feet shuffling)
(jacket rustling)
(Castor humming)
(timer whizzing)
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
Ba, ba, ba (panel beeping)
(timer whizzing)
(panel beeping)
- [Cartoon] Oh, baby, oh.
(device beeping)
(lid clattering)
- That was the scene at
the LA Convention Center,
where an FBI agent became a city savior.
Sean Archer disarmed a
massive bomb just one second
before it was set to blow.
The apparent targets were
three Supreme Court justices
scheduled to speak here today
and anyone unlucky enough to
be within a mile of the scene.
We asked Agent Archer
if the FBI had any leads
on who planted the device.
- Well, that is, uh,
classified information.
But if he, if he's listening,
I wouldn't mind giving him a message.
Interception, now our
side's got the ball, sorry.
(dramatic music)
(footsteps plodding)
(Sean whimpering)
(coworkers applauding)
Wanda, everybody, hey, look.
I, I wanna thank you
for, uh, enduring all these years
that I was an insufferable bore.
(coworkers laughing)
- Sir, did you just have
a surgical procedure?
What do you mean?
- Well, was the stick successfully
removed from your ass?
(coworkers laughing)
(Castor laughing)
- Sir, the White House on
one, it's the president,
oh, and your wife on line two.
Well, you tell the president to hold.
[Coworker] Okay.
(hand thudding)
(coworker gasps)
(Castor grunts)
(fingers tapping)
(computers beeping)
(gentle piano music)
(door clattering)
(bag thudding)
(gentle piano music continues)
Ooh, oh, my God.
Sean, you scared the hell out of me.
It's date night.
Oh, congratulations.
Oh, big deal.
(lips smacking)
Okay, I said, uh, "Mr
President, I want the authority,
and I want the funds, and the personnel
to take over the whole gamut
of global terrorism," right?
And he said, "The next name
on my calling list is Lazarro,
and I'm telling him
that Sean Archer writes
his own ticket, okay?"
(Eve sighing)
What's the matter?
I, I don't know, Sean.
You just, you just seem so different.
Hmm.
I mean, what is this, all this about,
what, this intimate
candlelight dinner, huh?
And I'm supposed to
forget all the promises
'cause you're going back into the fray?
(Eve sighing)
(gentle piano music continues)
- If the top cop in this
country can't come home
every night to his wife,
then to hell with the country
because the only place I'm
going is upstairs with you.
(lips smacking)
(gentle piano music continues)
(door clattering)
- Exercise, one hour.
(brooding music)
(baton clanking)
(inmate laughing)
(inmates chattering indistinctly)
- How can I get out of here?
(suspenseful music)
Ya can't.
[Sean] How can I get these boots off?
They only take 'em off in the clinic
right before they fry your skull.
Hey.
(suspenseful music continues)
I'm out of cigarettes.
Get back in line, Troy.
I said I'm out of cigarettes.
(fists thudding)
(dramatic music)
(bodies thudding)
(inmates cheering)
(fist thudding)
(batons thudding)
Kick his ass.
(foot thudding)
(Sean grunting)
(cigarette thudding)
(feet thudding)
(brooding music)
(batons thudding)
Hey, what the hell? That's not right.
(hands thudding)
(body thudding)
(Sean groaning)
(dramatic music continues)
I need a light.
(grunts) I need a light.
Anybody got a light?
- All right.
Got a light?
(inmates cheering)
(door slamming)
(switch clanking)
(electricity buzzing)
(Dubov groaning)
(dial clicking)
(machine whirring)
(electricity buzzing)
Better bring the bastard down
before he chokes himself to death.
(Dubov groaning)
(feet rasping)
(metal clanging)
(footsteps plodding)
(feet rasping)
(body thudding)
(footsteps plodding)
Well, happy day, it's Castor Troy.
(device clanking)
Wait. Hold it, hold it.
Can I, uh, can I have a light?
- You know, those things'll
kill you. (laughing)
Get his boots, Walton.
(metal clanging)
(suspenseful music)
Dubov, I didn't touch your wife.
And I didn't touch your sister.
But I know your wife loves
you, is waiting for you.
So let's get outta here.
(Dubov mumbles)
- You're more brain-dead
than Dubov. (laughing)
(electricity buzzing)
(doctor grunting)
(stone thudding)
(dramatic music)
(body thudding)
(foot thudding)
- Out.
[Guard] Get him.
(fists thudding)
(alarm blaring)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(alarm blaring)
- [Guard] Shots have been
fired. We have men down in C-4.
(computer beeping)
[Guard] I got 'em.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(glass shattering)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(door clattering)
(bodies thudding)
Move.
(gunshots blasting)
(alarm blaring)
(gun clanking)
(air whooshing)
(gunshot blasting)
(explosion blasting)
(guard screaming)
(body thudding)
(alarm blaring)
(dramatic music continues)
[Dubov] Get down.
(gunshots blasting)
(footsteps plodding)
(alarm blaring)
(inmates yelling indistinctly)
(feet and fists thudding)
(gunshots blasting)
(door clattering)
(dramatic music continues)
Dubov, no.
Get out.
(fingers tapping)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(knife slicing)
(Dubov screaming)
(fingers tapping)
(computer beeping)
(gun thudding)
(fingers tapping)
(computer beeping)
(electricity buzzing)
(gun thudding)
(computer beeping)
(electricity buzzing)
(guard screaming)
(inmates yelling indistinctly)
(gunshots blasting)
(explosion blasting)
Dubov.
(Dubov grunting)
(dramatic music continues)
Now, give me your hand.
Come on.
You can do it.
(explosions blasting)
No, no.
(gunshots blasting)
(fists thudding)
(inmates yelling indistinctly)
(electricity screeching)
(dramatic music continues)
(fists thudding)
(electricity buzzing)
(body thudding)
(hands thudding)
No, no.
(helicopter whirring)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(helicopter whirring)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(water splashing)
(helicopter whirring)
- Sean.
(rain pattering)
Wait.
(door clattering)
(umbrella clattering)
What are you doing?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
(lips smacking)
Have a nice day.
Have a nice day?
What is with you?
Is this your way of just not
dealing with this morning?
Yeah, yeah, maybe.
Sean, Sean.
I know it's hard for you,
but it's hard for me, too,
and we still have to go.
(birds chirping)
(somber music)
(hand rasping)
(toys clanking)
Happy birthday, Mikey.
He took our baby, Sean.
He took our little boy. (sobbing)
You turned your beeper off.
Yes, well, my son's birthday.
- Well, uh, here's some
poetic justice, sir.
Castor Troy is dead.
- He got killed trying
to escape from Erewhon.
Where's his body?
I, I wanna see his body.
It hasn't been recovered yet.
It hasn't been recovered yet?
Get the LAPD on this.
- Even if he is alive,
Castor isn't stupid enough
to come back to the city.
(Castor sighing)
- You must, you must trust me.
(brooding music)
He's already here.
(door clattering)
(suspenseful music)
(door squeaking)
(engine humming)
(car beeping)
(footsteps plodding)
(suspenseful music continues)
(door clattering)
(engine revving)
(phone beeping)
- [Receptionist] County General,
how may I direct your call?
Dr. Archer, please, it's an emergency.
[Receptionist] May I say who's calling?
Her husband.
- [Receptionist] Dr.
Archer, call on line three.
I know this sounds crazy, but, shit.
(phone clanking)
- Sean?
- Eve, listen carefully.
The man you think is your husband isn't.
- Who is this?
- Please, just listen.
Take Jamie.
Go to your mother's.
Don't tell him where you're going.
Just go.
Uh, whoever you are, don't call again.
(phone clanking)
(phone beeping)
(suspenseful music continues)
[Officer] Operations.
I need Victor Lazarro immediately.
[Officer] Regarding?
I have information about Castor Troy.
[(Officer] I'Il transfer you, sir.
Sean Archer here, who's calling?
- Well, if you're Sean Archer,
I guess I'm Castor Troy.
(phone clanking)
Ah, yes.
- [Reporter] This escaped
convict is considered
extremely dangerous.
If you have any information
concerning the whereabouts
of Castor Troy.
(switch clicking)
(siren wailing)
(engine humming)
You goddamn right, yeah.
(bell ringing)
This shit's so good,
gonna make your dick hard.
Huh?
Cheryl? Cheryl's a liar.
Dietrich.
So you're still selling hops and drugs
to Cheryl and Phil Roy.
(phone clanking)
(Dietrich laughing)
Castor fucking Troy.
Aw, man, you scared me, man.
All right, all right. (laughs)
- You know, I never should've
sold you those bombs.
It's my curse I can't say no to a friend.
- You can't say no to money.
- Yeah, that's my other curse.
You drug dealer.
- What's the matter?
- What?
- You look like you
just fucked your mother.
Come on. Let's go relax, huh?
Come on. (laughing)
♪ A Christian curse yourselves, oh ♪
♪ The devil in Helsinki ♪
- Hey.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Christian curse yourselves ♪
(Dietrich laughing)
Hey, Castor.
- Oh, who is this?
- Castor Troy.
What are you doing?
Whoo, hoo, hoo.
(friend laughing)
♪ Asking questions ♪
- Want a hit?
♪ Better start the instructions ♪
Hey, baby, remember me?
I'm your favorite peach.
(hand thudding)
Oh, I thought I was your favorite.
♪ You make me cringe ♪
Look at this guy.
You know, you look pretty
good for a dead guy.
Hey.
(suspenseful music)
Mescal, here.
So what do you wanna do?
(guns clanking)
(suspenseful music continues)
You wanna get out of the country?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm gonna get Sean Archer with your help.
Okay.
♪ I create my own, buy my own ♪
(glasses clinking)
Welcome home, baby.
♪ I imagine you'll manage ♪
♪ And in the meantime, I create my own ♪
(brooding music)
(glass thudding)
(Dietrich laughing)
How we supposed to do that?
He's vulnerable at home.
- No, I mean, this is Sean
Archer we're talking about.
This isn't just some Boy Scout.
- Fitch.
- Well, no, besides,
his house is probably
alarmed up the wazoo.
Code is 10-19-86.
That's his dead son's birthday.
Don't it just break your heart?
(Dietrich laughing)
That's brilliant.
That's sick.
(women laughing)
How is it that you know
so much about Sean Archer?
Uh, I, uh, sleep
with his wife.
(Dietrich laughing)
(all laughing)
This is, this is great.
So, once we kidnap supercop, then what?
Tiny surgery.
I'd like to take his, his face off.
Yes.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to use the little
boy's wee-wee room.
Cas.
You wanna take his face-
Yes, his face off.
Eyes, nose, skin, it's coming off.
Face off.
(body thudding)
No more drugs for that man.
(both laughing)
(water sloshing)
(dramatic music)
(air whooshing)
I'm not me.
I'm me.
Not me, me.
Castor, Archer, Castor, Archer.
I thought you were dead.
I'm not dead. I'm me.
(hand slapping)
(body thudding)
No, no, no, look.
What I, what I'm trying to
tell you, Brother, Pollux,
is once we get the full
protection and resources
of the government to help us
get rid of our rivals, right,
then we'll be set.
Then, maybe, just maybe,
(tires screeching)
I'll get my fricking face back.
Then, I'll just have one
jag-off to take care of.
(brooding rock music)
(door clattering)
Hey, where ya going?
Where ya going?
Karl, stop it.
- Maybe two, hold on.
- Karl, stop it.
- Calm down, would ya?
- Karl.
- Calm down.
- Karl, my dad's home.
Let go.
Happy hunting, I'll catch ya later.
- Stop it.
- Yeah,
like Mr. Fucking Invisible
gives a shit about you anyway.
So fucking hold still.
(Jamie screaming)
(glass shattering)
(Karl grunting)
(body thudding)
(hands thudding)
(foot thudding)
(Karl whimpering)
(body thudding)
(Karl groaning)
- Okay, say you're sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- I didn't hear it.
- Mean it.
- I'm so sorry.
(body thudding)
(Castor exhales)
(case clanking)
Dress up like Halloween,
and ghouls will try to get in your pants.
(lighter clicking)
Typical, Dad.
Some guy tries to rape
me, and I'm to blame?
(case clanking)
(lighter clicking)
This isn't you. (sighs)
Now, you haven't been
the same since Mike died,
hiding behind someone else's face,
hoping you wouldn't feel the pain.
While we're talking,
do you have protection?
What, do you mean like condoms?
(knife clanking)
(brooding music)
Protection.
Next time, let Karl take his pants down.
Slip this in his thigh, twist
it so the wound won't close.
(knife clanking)
(brooding music continues)
Now, go on. Get outta here.
(Castor sighing)
I am the king.
(Sean moans)
(Sasha moans)
Eve.
(hands thudding)
(Sasha screams)
(gun clanking)
- Jesus, Cas, it's me.
It's me.
Cas, shh.
Come on. It's me.
Jesus.
(gun thudding)
Come on.
No, don't, don't you wanna talk?
- The only talk I ever heard
from you is suck my tongue,
I love your ass, and see ya.
Take this filthy shit off, put
this on, and get outta here.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, really?
What, do you, what, do you
expect me, after all this time,
just to, just to jump on you?
- That's not what I-
- Is that what you expect?
That's not what I meant.
What did you mean?
- L meant-
- Huh?
Is this what you meant, hmm?
That, that, how about this?
Is that good, hmm?
(dramatic music)
(phone ringing)
(phone clanking)
- Sean Archer.
- Bro.
Well, I figured he might drop
in on some of our old friends.
And if my eyes don't deceive,
I think this fellow's
beginning to enjoy being you.
Good.
(phone clanking and beeping)
(lips smacking)
Look, look, look, okay, look, Sasha.
What I meant is, uh, that
I'm not going anywhere
until your brother helps me, uh, first.
(Sasha exhales)
- Cas, if the FBI finds
out that you were here,
I'll lose my son.
Please, Cas, you just gotta go.
(pensive music)
I've said and done some things
that have made your life harder.
I know.
- How would you?
When you left, you never looked back.
I, I just know.
(door squeaking)
Look, Sasha, I'm not the
same person you remember.
And for what it's worth, I'm sorry.
They're nice-looking clothes.
Yeah, of course, they're yours.
Oh, I know, I just like 'em.
He's a nice-looking kid, too.
Yeah, of course.
He's yours, too.
(dramatic music)
(dispatcher speaking indistinctly)
(guns clanking)
(gentle music)
- How old is he?
- Five.
Nobody knows he's yours.
I was scared someone would try
to hurt him just to hurt you.
Adam, Adam.
(guns clanking)
(guns thudding)
Don't want you playing with those things.
They are very, very dangerous, okay?
Now, come on, sweetie.
I want you to meet your father.
Look at him. It's okay.
Say hi.
[Adam] Hi.
(wistful music)
(Sean laughing)
Hi, Michael.
Michael, Michael?
- Cas, Cas.
- Michael.
- Cas, you're scaring him.
Let him go.
What is the matter with you?
(gunshot blasting)
[Sean] Get down.
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
(gunshots blasting)
(gang members screaming)
(glass shattering)
Okay, Red Team, Red Team, break off.
How'd you get to be so brave?
(gunshots blasting)
(headset clanking)
- [Officer] Come out
now with your hands up.
Put these on.
[Sasha] Okay, that's a good idea, baby.
Listen to your music.
Come on.
- Come out now.
♪ Somewhere ♪
- Go, go, go.
- We have a warrant
for your arrest.
(glass shattering)
Cops.
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
I hate cops.
(gunshot blasting)
(woman screaming)
Come on, kid.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
Move, move.
Go left, left, first door to the right.
(glass shattering)
(gunshots blasting)
Go, go, go.
(door clattering)
Go, go.
(bullets whizzing)
(gunshots blasting)
(body thudding)
♪ Someday I'll wish upon a star ♪
♪ And wake up ♪
- Let's get out of here.
(bullets whizzing)
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(vase shattering)
Damn, my place is getting fucked up.
(Castor laughing)
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
(woman screaming)
Take him.
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
(foot thudding)
(hand thudding)
(body thudding)
Cas, Cas, give me the boy.
(gunshots blasting)
Really? Really?
(officer screaming)
Shit.
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
Cas, be careful with him.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(officer screams)
- [Dietrich] Don't be
scared, all right, all right?
♪ Somewhere over the rainbow ♪
(gunshots blasting)
♪ Skies are blue ♪
♪ And the dreams that you dared to dream ♪
♪ Really do come true ♪
(gunshots blasting)
♪ Someday I'll wish upon a star ♪
♪ And wake up where the clouds ♪
♪ Are far behind me ♪
- Adam.
♪ Birds fly over the rainbow ♪
♪ Why then, oh, why can't I ♪
(gunshots blasting)
- Adam, Adam.
(dramatic music)
Get him out back.
Go, go, go.
Put the boy down.
Honey, sweetie, don't touch that.
(foot thudding)
It isn't nice.
(body thudding)
I don't ever wanna see you do that.
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music)
(Dietrich laughing)
- They're like cockroaches.
(gunshots blasting)
Hey, drop it.
(gun thudding)
That's it.
(gun clanking)
Buzz.
[Officer] Hey.
(gun thudding)
(Sean grunting)
(gunshot blasting)
Told him not to fuck with me.
(suspenseful music)
(gun clanking)
(suspenseful music continues)
(gunshot blasting)
Take the boy and get outta here.
- Are you all right?
- Go.
(lips smacking)
Hurry up.
(footsteps plodding)
Hey, man.
We had some good times, didn't we?
(Dietrich groaning)
(gun clanking)
(footsteps plodding)
(gunshots blasting)
(air whooshing)
(glass shattering)
(gun thudding)
(suspenseful music)
(Castor sighing)
I don't know what I hate wearing worse,
your face or your body.
I mean, I enjoy boning your wife,
but, uh, well, let's face it.
We both like it better the other way, yes?
So why don't we just trade back?
- You can't give back
what you've taken from me.
Oh, well, plan B.
Let's just kill each other.
(air whooshing)
(suspenseful music continues)
(gunshots blasting)
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music continues)
(explosions blasting)
(fire roaring)
(door clattering)
(dramatic music continues)
(bodies thudding)
(Pollux grunting)
(glass shattering)
(body thudding)
(gunshots blasting)
(somber music)
(somber music continues)
Sir, why are you so upset?
It's just Pollux Troy.
(gunshot blasting)
(body thudding)
(somber music continues)
(glass crunching)
- Sir, look, you're on the
cover of "Time." (laughs)
Listen.
"In a single week, Agent
Sean Archer has ordered
a stunning series of
blitzkrieg-style raids
on the hideouts, staging
grounds, and safe houses
of our nation's assassins, car bombers."
(door slamming)
(body thudding)
(door clattering)
Sean, look, we're friends,
so I'm gonna tell you face to face.
I don't give a damn if you
are "Time's" Man of the Year.
After last night's bloodbath,
I'm terminating your war on terrorists.
(suspenseful music)
(Victor groans)
- Is that, uh, because
I'm getting all the kudos,
and you're not?
Jesus Christ, I don't know
where you're getting your intelligence.
It's not from field agents.
Sometimes I think you know too much.
Washington's starting to worry.
Justice wants a hearing.
They're concerned about
the constitutionality
of your gestapo tactics, and
frankly, so am I. (grunts)
- Uh, okay, Victor, I'll give
the, uh, taxpayers a break.
But, um,
I have something, uh, I want to confess.
And I don't think you're gonna like it.
I am Castor Troy.
(hand thudding)
(dramatic music)
(fist thudding)
(Victor grunting)
(head thudding)
(Castor sighing)
(phone clanking)
Kimmy.
Kim?
- Yes, sir.
Call the paramedics.
Victor Lazarro's had a heart attack.
- Oh, God, right away.
- Thank you.
(phone clanking)
(Castor sighing)
(pensive music)
(sprinklers clattering)
(dog barking)
(officer speaking faintly)
(door squeaking)
(Sean exhaling)
Home.
(Sean grunting)
(water pattering)
(pensive music continues)
(drawer clattering)
(purse thudding)
(towel rustling)
Eve.
No, honey, please, please don't scream.
Don't scream.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay, just don't, don't, don't, don't.
Just don't, don't look at my face.
And the voice, don't listen.
- Just-
- I know who you are.
You killed our son.
- Sh, sh.
I did not kill our son, sh, sh.
I'm Sean.
(Eve whimpering and gasping)
The last time I saw you was in this room.
We had a fight when I said
I had to go away again.
And I spent the night in Mike's old bed.
(footsteps plodding)
(Sean gasping)
I'm tired, Eve.
The assignment was to enter a
federal prison as Castor Troy.
It's just fucking insane.
And it's, a special ops
surgeon, uh, gave me,
uh, Castor's face.
(hand thudding)
Then, uh, and then, somehow, Castor came
out of his, uh, his, his coma,
and he killed everybody
who knew about the mission
but, but not before transforming into me.
(melancholic music)
(fist thudding)
(glass shattering)
(Eve screams)
(photo rustling)
I know you don't believe
a word I'm saying.
Well, here's proof, Doctor.
Your husband, me, my, Sean's
blood type is O-negative.
Castor's is AB.
And I love you.
(footsteps plodding)
(door clattering)
(melancholic music continues)
(dispatcher speaking indistinctly)
Get some backup.
(door clattering)
What a day.
(footsteps plodding)
You look tense.
(suspenseful music)
I know I've been acting
different lately, strange.
I've got a confession to make, Eve.
You're not gonna like it.
Oh, Eve, I feel, I feel so close to you.
I read your diary.
I know I shouldn't have.
I'm ashamed, but I did.
I just wanna be the man
that, that you deserve,
passionate, tender.
Victor Lazarro died today.
He had a heart seizure,
my mentor, gone.
(pensive music)
(sighs) First Tito, then Victor, so what?
I hope this doesn't mean I'm losing you.
Of course not.
(lips smacking)
You're the only family I've got.
(pensive music continues)
(syringe rasping)
(engine humming)
(pensive music continues)
(syringe clanking)
(slides clanking)
(suspenseful music)
(computer beeping)
Oh, God. (exhales)
Oh, God.
I was hoping you'd come here.
Thank you for trusting me.
(gun clanking)
Right now, I don't trust anyone.
Eve, where'd you get that gun?
I took it from my fake husband.
Put it down.
You know I'm Sean.
Do I?
Maybe Sean's already dead, huh?
I'm moving very slowly.
(gentle music)
(Sean whimpering)
(Sean laughing)
I was thinking the other day.
I, I remember.
I once took a date out for surf and turf,
not knowing she was a vegetarian.
So she ate bread
and, uh, and broke her tooth
on a (laughing) rye seed.
And we, we drove around all night,
uh, looking for a, for
a, an all-night dentist.
And, and he, uh, he was so drunk
(laughing) he fixed the wrong tooth.
And it, when I finally brought her home,
even though it must have hurt like hell,
you, you, you kissed me.
(gentle music continues)
(Eve whimpering)
Sean, that man,
you know we've been living together
as man and wife for a week.
Eve, Eve, I put you in that position,
and, and I, I, I can
never make it up to you.
Well, you're damn well gonna try.
Let me take a look at that
wound before you bleed to death.
(air whooshing)
(bedding rustling)
With Lazarro out of the way,
Castor's the new acting
director of the Bureau.
He's untouchable.
- Not tomorrow.
Tomorrow he'll be at Victor's service.
Tomorrow.
That will be the day.
(suspenseful music)
I want you and Jamie away from there.
Give him a good excuse.
I can cover for Jamie,
but if I'm not coming, he's
gonna know that something's up.
And besides, I'm the only one
who can try and explain the truth.
(lips smacking)
- [Receptionist] Excuse me,
Mr. Archer, may I help you?
Dr. Levine to X-ray.
(curtains rustling)
(blanket rustling)
Sean, what are you doing here?
(machine beeping)
Oh, oh, sorry, darling,
I just get so, so jealous.
I, I mean, what is a guy to think
when his, uh, his wife runs
off in the middle of the night?
That I'm a doctor that's on call,
so please let me get back to work, okay?
Sorry.
(lips smacking)
Lies, distrust, mixed messages,
this is turning into a real marriage.
(machine beeping)
(waves lapping)
(brooding music)
(birds squawking)
(footsteps plodding)
How's Adam?
I took him over to my cousin's
until this whole thing blows over.
Where's Jamie?
That's what I'd like to know.
She stole $50 from my purse and took off.
(gun clanking)
So what's the next move?
This isn't your fight.
Oh, come on. You're surprised?
Our daughter won't even
visit Michael's grave.
You think she gives a
damn about your boss?
(door clattering)
(suspenseful music continues)
He killed my brother.
I'm not gonna let him take you, too.
- Whatever happens, I promise
(gentle music)
Sean Archer is off your back for good.
(waves lapping)
(birds squawking)
- My dear friends, we
are here to celebrate
the life of Victor Lazarro.
(priest speaking Latin)
Amen.
(vocalists singing in Latin)
(priest speaking Latin)
(wings fluttering)
(vocalists singing in Latin)
(air whooshing)
(wings fluttering)
(vocalists singing in Latin)
(vocalists continue singing in Latin)
(photo rustling)
- Somebody back there asked
me to give this to you.
(vocalists continue singing in Latin)
(wings fluttering)
(photo rustling)
- [Priest] In peace now, let
us take our brother Victor
to his place of rest.
(photo rustling)
(vocalists singing in Latin)
(footsteps plodding)
(wings fluttering)
(gun clanking)
(suspenseful music)
(Castor singing in Latin)
Isn't this religious?
Ah, ah, yes.
The eternal battle between good
and evil, saint and sinner.
But you're still not having any fun.
(gunshots blasting)
(gun clanking)
(Castor laughing)
Honey, honey. (laughing)
Come here.
Ah.
And guess what.
Your daughter's on the way.
History repeats itself.
(hand thudding)
(footsteps plodding)
(engine humming)
(tires screeching)
This is between us.
Leave them out of it.
No, you should've left them out of it.
Your son was an accident.
I wanted to kill you.
But you took it so personally.
Why didn't you just kill
yourself or let it go?
No father could.
No brother could either.
Neither could a sister.
Hey, baby.
(guns clanking)
Sasha, what the fuck are you doing here?
Gee, Archer, I guess I'm crashing.
You okay, baby?
Yeah, thanks.
Sasha, baby.
I'm Castor. That's Archer.
And I'm bored.
(Castor sighing)
Put the fucking gun down.
- [Gangster] Why don't
you put your guns down?
(Castor laughing)
Wee, (laughs) what a predicament.
(air whooshing)
(suspenseful music continues)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music)
(wings fluttering)
(gunshots blasting)
(Eve screaming)
(dramatic music continues)
(wings fluttering)
(pensive music)
Take care of our boy.
You love him so much.
Don't let him grow up
to be like us, promise?
- Yeah.
- Say yeah.
(pensive music continues)
(footsteps plodding)
(gunshots blasting)
(dramatic music)
(glass shattering)
Mom?
(gunshots blasting)
(Jamie screaming)
Jamie.
(feet thudding)
(gunshots blasting)
(Jamie screaming)
Jamie, go.
(gunshots blasting)
(Jamie screaming)
Hello, Wanda?
Wanda, this is Eve Archer.
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
I have something crazy to tell you.
(wings fluttering)
(both grunting)
(bodies thudding)
(fists thudding)
It's a capital crime to try to kill
the next big boss of the FBI, yes?
- Yes.
- Ah, yes.
The penalty-
- What?
- The penalty is death.
(elbow thudding)
(gun clanking)
(gun thudding)
(bodies thudding)
Die.
Please, God, die.
- Hold it.
(gun clanking)
Ah, good girl, Jamie.
Shoot him.
Honey, don't listen to him, honey.
He's not your father.
Hear my voice. I'm your father.
Use your eyes, Jamie. Shoot him.
Don't listen to him. Don't shoot.
Just, just-
- This scumbag,
this scumbag shot your brother, Jamie.
Kill him.
(gunshot blasting)
(Sean grunting)
Clod.
No daughter of mine would shoot so wide.
Dad, put the gun down.
Put it down.
(footsteps plodding)
Dad, put it down.
Now, we're gonna find
out what's in papa's bag.
Peaches.
(Jamie whimpering)
(suspenseful music)
Say goodbye to papa.
(knife clanking)
(Jamie grunting)
(knife slicing)
(Castor screaming)
Jamie.
(gate clanging)
(gunshots blasting)
(siren wailing)
(dramatic music continues)
Jamie, Jamie.
Jamie, are you all right?
Oh, my God.
Sir, are you okay?
(gunshots blasting)
(body thudding)
(gun clanking)
(siren wailing)
(dramatic music continues)
(sobbing) Please, someone please
tell me what planet I'm on.
(gun clanking)
(gunshots blasting)
(boater screaming)
(water splashing)
(engine revving)
(gunshot blasting)
(gunshots blasting)
Get down.
(engine revving)
(explosion blasting)
(water sloshing)
(dramatic music)
(horn blaring)
(engines revving)
(boat thudding)
(water splashing)
(boats thudding)
(engines revving)
(dramatic music continues)
(gunshots blasting)
(gasoline sloshing)
Stop, this is the police.
Stop immediately, or we'll
be forced to open fire.
(gunshots blasting)
Fire. Fire.
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music continues)
(gunshots blasting)
(body thudding)
(boats thudding)
(Sean screaming)
(engine revving)
(dramatic music continues)
(wood clattering)
(fire roaring)
(explosion blasting)
(engine revving)
(dramatic music continues)
(engines roaring)
(gasoline sloshing)
(fire crackling)
(dramatic music continues)
(explosion blasting)
(both grunting)
(engine roaring)
(Sean grunting)
(engine revving)
(dramatic music continues)
(air whooshing)
(anchor whooshing)
(body thudding)
(anchor thudding)
(glass shattering)
(fist thudding)
(water splashing)
(chain clanging)
(dramatic music continues)
(engine revving)
(water splashing)
(dramatic music continues)
(fists thudding)
(foot thudding)
(body thudding)
(Sean grunting)
(hand thudding)
(rope snapping)
(anchor rasping)
(water splashing)
(dramatic music continues)
(boat thudding)
(water splashing)
(explosion blasting)
(items clattering)
(fire crackling)
(hands thudding)
(fist thudding)
(dramatic music)
(foot thudding)
(Castor grunting)
(body thudding)
(knife rasping)
(knife slashing)
(Sean groaning)
(pipe thudding)
(body thudding)
(dramatic music continues)
(pipe thudding)
(Sean groaning)
(body thudding)
(foot thudding)
(metal clanging)
(harpoon slicing)
(Castor screaming)
(Castor gasping)
You're right, Sean.
I've misbehaved.
I need to be punished.
(metal clanging)
(dramatic music)
But remember, every time
you look in the mirror,
you'll see my face.
(knife slicing)
(dramatic music continues)
(trigger clanking)
(foot thudding)
(Castor groaning)
(metal clanging)
(Castor grunting)
Die.
(Castor gasping)
(harpoon gun thudding)
(footsteps plodding)
(body thudding)
♪ Ready ♪
♪ Ready for the big ride, baby ♪
(sirens wailing)
- [Dispatcher] Off of Pico
in the middle of the street.
(dispatcher speaking indistinctly)
(door clattering)
(footsteps plodding)
You okay, Archer?
(gentle music)
What did you call me?
He called you Archer, sir.
(gurney rattling)
- Sean, they're bringing in
their top surgical team from DC.
You're gonna be okay.
(gentle music continues)
(gurney clattering)
(siren wailing)
(Jamie sobbing)
(machine beeping and whirring)
- [Doctor] When you wake up,
everything will be restored
just the way it was.
My scar, the one near my heart,
this old bullet wound, I
won't need it any more.
[Doctor] Okay.
(air whooshing)
(fingers tapping)
(gentle music continues)
(Eve sighing)
(footsteps plodding)
(door clattering)
(uplifting music)
Dad?
(lips smacking)
I'm sorry I shot you.
- I've got something I
have to ask both of you.
(gentle music)
This is, um, Adam, and
he needs a place to live.
Hi, my name's Jamie.
I'm Adam.
Why don't you show Adam his new room?
Come on.
Okay.
(uplifting music)
(uplifting music continues)
(upbeat music)
♪ You shot your mouth off like a kid ♪
♪ Who's scared to have a heart ♪
♪ You're loosing grip
of what really matters ♪
♪ 'Cause you don't know where to start ♪
♪ You wake up in the morning ♪
♪ With a starfuck for a friend ♪
♪ The things you do are so in tune ♪
♪ With what you got and hate ♪
♪ What's giving you the will to live ♪
♪ Is looking for revenge ♪
♪ The only laugh that you've got left ♪
♪ Is hiding from the pain ♪
♪ What must have happened to your soul ♪
♪ Is skinning you alive ♪
♪ The thing that you
fear the most is love ♪
♪ And that's buried deep inside, yeah ♪
♪ So deep inside ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't do the time ♪
♪ But can you pay the price ♪
♪ The heart you're building out of rock ♪
♪ Is turning into sand ♪
♪ 'Cause you never took
the time to think ♪
♪ What it means to be a man ♪
♪ You act like you got the answers ♪
♪ When the question's never asked ♪
♪ I've been to where you're coming from ♪
♪ But the postcards weren't so bad ♪
♪ The knife I carry's been sharpened ♪
♪ On the mouths that wont keep shut ♪
♪ I'll stab at you in the darkness ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm trying to shed some light ♪
♪ Your point of view's so meaningless ♪
♪ If you ever had one at all ♪
♪ All you seem to care about ♪
♪ Is who's gonna take the fall ♪
♪ Who's gonna take the fall for you ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ Now, I can't do the time for ya ♪
♪ Can you pay the price ♪
(energetic music continues)
♪ Yeah, my, my, my, my ♪
(vocalist speaking indistinctly)
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't do the time ♪
♪ But can you pay the price ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't do the time ♪
♪ Can you pay the price ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ If you can't do the time ♪
♪ No, don't lose your head ♪
♪ You can't pay the price ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ No, I can't do the time ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Worry about today ♪
♪ Don't lose your head ♪
♪ And worry about your man ♪